afbank.com 2008-12-17

# Armed Forces Bank, N.A. || Privacy Policy Statement

| 

Privacy Policy Statement

Protecting your financial and personal privacy is important to us!

Our policy is to protect personal or financial information which comes into our possession during the normal course of business. The following privacy guidelines serve as standards our employees will use when collecting, using, and maintaining your personal information. 

1\. RECOGNITION OF YOUR EXPECTATION OF PRIVACY

We recognize the importance of keeping your personal and financial information accurate and confidential at all times. We handle this information carefully because we value the trust you place in us when you decide to become our customer.

2\. CATEGORIES OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT

We collect personal and financial information about you from the following sources: 

  * Information we receive from you on applications or other forms
  * Information about your transactions with us or other third parties
  * Information we receive from a consumer reporting agency

3\. COLLECTION, RETENTION, AND USE OF CUSTOMER INFORMATION

We collect, retain, and use information about you in accordance with regulatory requirements, to enhance the quality of service and products we provide, and to inform you about additional opportunities that may be beneficial. 

4\. CATEGORIES OF INFORMATION WE DISCLOSE AND PERSONS TO WHOM WE DISCLOSE INFORMATION 

We do not disclose any personal or financial information about you to anyone, except as permitted by law. For example, we are permitted by law to disclose personal or financial information about you in the following circumstances: 

  * To reputable information reporting agencies such as credit bureaus
  * In order to complete a transaction initiated by you
  * At your request
  * In response to legal process (for example, a subpoena that complies with applicable right to financial privacy laws)
  * To persons who provide us with products or services that help us furnish banking services to you (for example, check printers, appraisers, loan processors, etc.)

If you decide to close your account(s) or become an inactive customer, we will continue to adhere to the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

5\. MAINTAINING CUSTOMER PRIVACY IN BUSINESS RELATIONSHIPS WITH THIRD PARTIES

We may disclose all of the information we collect, as described above, to companies that provide us with products or services that help us furnish banking services to you (for example, check printers, appraisers, loan processors, etc.). If we do so, the recipients of such information must agree in writing to maintain standards of confidentiality similar to our standards and to use the information only for the purposes for which it was disclosed.  
We may also disclose such information to other financial institutions with which we have joint marketing agreements. 

6\. MAINTENANCE OF ACCURATE INFORMATION 

We continually strive to maintain complete and accurate information about you and your accounts. If you ever believe that our records contain inaccurate or incomplete information, please notify us. We will investigate your concerns and correct any inaccuracies. 

7\. CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY 

We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with Federal regulations to guard your personal and financial information. Our employees do not have access to your personal or financial information unless they have a business reason to have access to this information. We educate our employees on the importance of maintaining the confidentiality of your personal and financial information and on this Privacy Policy.

8\. DISCLOSURE OF PRIVACY POLICY TO CUSTOMERS

We recognize and respect your privacy expectations. We want you to understand our commitment to privacy in our use of your personal and financial information. Because of our commitment to you, we have developed this Privacy Policy and wish to make it readily available to you. 

9\. PRIVACY INFORMATION SPECIFIC TO INTERNET USAGE 

  1. When you visit our web site (www.afbank.com, www.academybankco.com, www.afbca.com), we want to assure you that we adhere to this Privacy Policy.
  2. We collect and store information about "hits" on our web site for internal review purposes only. Such information may include the name of the domain from which you access the Internet (such as AOL.com or ATT.net), the date and time you access our site, and the Internet address of the web site from which you linked to us. This information enables us to see how you use our web site and keep our web site user-friendly.
  3. Our web site may require you disclose any personally identifying information. If you do provide personal information, such as your mailing and e-mail address, telephone and fax numbers, or demographic and customer identification, we will not disclose (share, sell, or divulge) it except:
    * In order to complete a transaction initiated by you
    * At your request
    * In response to legal process (for example, a subpoena that complies with applicable right to financial privacy laws)
    * To persons who provide us with products or services that help us furnish banking services to you (for example, check printers, appraisers, loan processors, etc.)

  4. In order to provide better service, we will occasionally use a "cookie." A cookie is a small piece of information, which a web site stores on your PC for later retrieval. The cookie cannot be read by a web site other than the one that set the cookie. We use cookies for a number of administrative purposes, for example, to store preferences for certain kinds of information or to store a password so that it does not have to be input for every visit someone makes to our site. Most cookies last only through a single session, or visit. None will contain information that will enable anyone to contact the visitor via telephone, e-mail, orregular mail. In addition, web browsers can be set to inform the visitor when cookies are set or to prevent cookies from being set.
  5. We do not knowingly solicit information from children and we do not market specifically to children. We recognize that protecting children's identities and privacy on-line is important and that the responsibility to do so rests with parents and the on-line industry.
  6. Internet connections can be insecure and may provide the opportunity for the unauthorized interception, diversion, access or disclosure of your private information. Computers are regularly subjected to attacks by third-parties attempting to obtain unauthorized access to your private information through malicious software, malware, spyware or other electronic means. You are responsible for maintaining protection against unauthorized third-party access to your private information stored on or transmitted to and from your computer. Except as otherwise provided in the Account Terms and Conditions we are not responsible for any loss, financial loss, injury or damage, whether direct or indirect, special or consequential, arising in any way out of the installation, use or maintenance of your PC, electronic device or related software, including without limitation the use of any information obtained by a third-party from your PC by any means including that obtained by the use of any malicious computer code or program.

DISCLOSURES

This Privacy Policy will be provided to each new customer at the time the customer relationship is established. Additionally, a copy of this Privacy Policy will be mailed to all customers once per calendar year. Anyone may receive a copy of this Privacy Policy upon request. 

WE RESERVE THE RIGHT TO CHANGE THIS POLICY AT ANY TIME. 

Questions concerning the privacy of your information at any of our institutions should be directed to: 

Armed Forces Bank, N.A.  
Attention: Privacy Manager  
320 Kansas Avenue  
Fort Leavenworth, KS 66027  
Telephone: (913) 682-9090  
E-mail: [privacy@afbank.com](mailto:privacy@afbank.com)  

If you send e-mail to us, please remember that e-mail is not secure against interception. If your e-mail contains information that is very sensitive or includes personal information such as your account numbers, charge card number, or social security number, you may want to send this information via postal mail. 

THANK YOU FOR BANKING WITH US!

We understand how important your privacy is. We value the trust you place in us and will keep your personal and financial information confidential. 

|
